(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
サクラカゼ
作詞・作曲 ハム
Sakura Kaze
Lyrics/Composition: Hamu
にゃっはろー！
Nya-hello!
さくらみこ生誕祭2023
Sakura Miko Birthday Party 2023
はじまりよー！
Here we go!
箱にあたる陽を　横目で眺めて
Watching the sunlight hitting the box from the corner of my eye
そっと陰る木の根に　一人で比べてた
Quietly comparing myself to the shaded tree roots alone
積もる溜息を　吹き払うように
As if to blow away the accumulating sighs
そんな私を君が　見つけてくれたんだ
That's when you found me
そう　それは恋のような　ぬくもりを
Yes, it was a love-like warmth
君に笑顔咲かせたら
If I can make a smile bloom on you
桜風に踊る空 君と出会ったこの場所で
In the sky where the cherry blossom wind dances,
at this place where I met you
どれくらいの思い出ぎゅっと 溢れそうになるかな
I wonder how many memories will overflow
as I hold them tight?
君と流した涙は 明日の笑顔の糧にしよう
Let's turn the tears shed with you
into food for tomorrow's smiles
膝をついたって ほら 何度だっていいよ
Even if you fall on your knees,
look, it's okay any number of times
意地を張って 恥をかいて いじけたって それでも
Even if you're stubborn, feel ashamed,
or get sulky
君がそばで見守ってくれたこと
The fact that you watched over me by my side
わかってるから
Because I know
追い風を受けて とまらない日々も
Even in the non-stop days receiving a tailwind
そっと挫けそうになって 心が渦巻いた
Quietly feeling like I was about to give up,
my heart was in a whirlpool
積もる溜息でまた 泣きかけても
Even if I'm about to cry again with accumulating sighs
あたたかな手でずっと 支えてくれたんだ
You've always supported me with your warm hands
ほら 耳をすませば
Look, if you listen closely
一人じゃないから
Because you're not alone
諦めかけて心が閉じても
Even if your heart closes
as you're about to give up
君が背中を押してくれたよね
You pushed me from behind, didn't you?
春の蕾が花開く頃は
When the spring buds bloom
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
今年も祝ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for celebrating with me again this year
また来年もお祝いしようね
Let's celebrate next year too
隣で笑い合おうね
Let's laugh together by each other's side
桜風に踊る空 君と出会ったこの場所で
In the sky where the cherry blossom wind dances,
at this place where I met you
どれくらいの思い出ぎゅっと 溢れそうになるかな
I wonder how many memories will overflow
as I hold them tight?
君と描くこの花は 未来もきっと残るから
This flower I draw with you
will surely remain in the future too
汗をかいた分は そうさ 強くなれるんだ
The amount you sweat, yes, you can become stronger
意地を張って 恥をかいて いじけたって それでも
Even if you're stubborn, feel ashamed,
or get sulky
君がそばで見守ってくれたから
Because you watched over me by my side
ありがとうだよ
I say thank you
今日は楽しいライブにしようね みんな大好きだよ
Let's have a fun live today, I love you all
君と出会えたこの空 これからもっと咲かせるよ
This sky where I could meet you,
I'll make more bloom from now on
にゃっはろー！ゲストお披露目も盛りだくさん！盛り上がっていくぞー！
Nyahallo! Lots of guest reveals too!
Let's get hyped!
Glory Steady Go!
1, 2, 3 見つけちゃった 大事にしていたい思い
1, 2, 3 I found it, the feelings I want to cherish
ぎゅっと ぎゅっと 抱きしめなきゃ こぼれちゃいそう
I have to hold them tight or they might spill out
胸に秘めずに 放っていかなきゃね
I have to let them out without keeping them
in my heart
ほら ほら もっともっと かなでちゃいまショー！
Look, look, let's play them more and more,
it's showtime!
Ready go! Ready to be! Ready for line!
伝えたいのは 言葉だけじゃ足んないメロディー
What I want to convey is a melody that
words aren't enough for
溢れるリズムでいいじゃん
The overflowing rhythm is fine, isn't it?
耳を澄ませば ほら 夢トキメキかなら
Listen closely, and look, the dream
heart-throbbing will sound
なりたい自分へと 歌いたい歌
To the person I want to be, the song I want to sing
もっと もっと 胸に満ちていくから
Because it will fill my heart more and more
全力全開一歩ずつ 詰め込み進めてけ
At full power, step by step, pack it in and move forward
ウェイクアップ！空を 泣いちゃう自分を目指してゴー！
Wake up! Aim for the sky and the self
that would cry, and go!
その思い乗せて 歌よ響け
Carry those feelings, and let the song resonate
Glory Steady Go! Ready to smile!
Ready to go! Showtime! Wonderland Showtime!
La la la...
改めまして かくれんぼが得意な思い
Once again, the feelings that are good at hide-and-seek
いつものとこかな　ショータイム
Is it the usual place? Showtime
いつだってさ　忘れたくないな　ほらほら
I don't want to forget, anytime. Look, look
やっぱやっぱ　描きたいドリームに
I really, really want to draw the dream
コンニチハ
Hello
今すぐ　ワンツースリーで
Right now, with a one-two-three
ステップ踏んで　ワンツースリーの
Take a step, with a one-two-three
脳内ワンタイム　ショウで変身
One-time show in the brain, transformation
それはつまり　今しか鳴り得ないメロディ
That is to say, a melody that can only ring now
愛おしいのワンツーじゃん
Lovely one-two, right?
風を紡いで　淡い春弾け
Spinning the wind, faint spring pops
レッツゴー
Let's go
レッツショウ
Let's show
イッツショウタイム！
It's showtime!
会いに行けるよ　サイコー歌いたい　ハイ
I can go see you, I want to sing the best, high
もっともっと笑っちゃえ　キラキラトビきりみたいな
Smile more and more, like a sparkling leap
ステップステップ　雨が降っても　ほら　ミライ蒔いて　ファンウェイク
Step, step, even if it rains, look, sow the future, fun wake
叶う足跡は　消えやしないから
The footprints that come true will never disappear
空を見上げれば　虹がかかるよ　キミに
If you look up at the sky, a rainbow will appear for you
キミに響け
Echo to you
響け　クラップユアハンズ
Echo, clap your hands
不器用な音でも
Even with a clumsy sound
伝わろう　何気ないエブリデイ
Let's convey the casual everyday
それはシャイニーデイズ
That is shiny days
涙こぼれそう
Tears are about to fall
レッツゴー
Let's go
レッツショウ
Let's show
ワンダランショータイム！
Wonderland showtime!
会いに行けるよ　サイコー歌いたい　ハイ
I can go see you, I want to sing the best, high
もっともっと見て遊ぼう　あこがれたキミだったな
Let's look and play more and more, you were the one I admired
ステップステップ　一歩ずつ　ほら　ミライ蒔いて　ファンウェイク
Step, step, one step at a time, look, sow the future, fun wake
叶う　涙に自分を満たして
Fill yourself with tears that come true
その想い乗せて　歌よ響け
With those feelings, let the song echo
マイセンシングゴー
My sensing go
アイワナビー
I wanna be
居たいのはスマイル
What I want to stay is a smile
行きたいのは...
Where I want to go is...
行きたいのは招待　ワンダラン招待
What I want is an invitation, wonderland invitation
イェーイ！
Yay!
逃げてちゃダメ
Don't run away
避けてちゃダメ
Don't avoid it
後悔なんてしたくない
I don't want to regret anything
レッツゴ　ハッピー
Let's go happy
らしく進もう
Let's move on as ourselves
グッドデイ　目覚ましより
Good day, earlier than the alarm clock
早起きのサニーデイ
An early rising sunny day
今日はいつもよりそう
Today, more than usual, yes
ちょっとおしゃれ頑張った
I worked hard on dressing up a bit
なのに全然　君は全然
But you haven't, you haven't at all...
気づかないでよそ見してるんだ
Noticed and are looking away
知らない乙女心
A maiden's heart you don't know
教えてあげる
I'll teach it to you
君が好き！素直になって
I love you! Being honest
言えたらどんなに　ソーハッピー
How happy I'd be if I could say it
溢れ出すこの愛は
This overflowing love is
甘いだけではありません！
Not just sweet!
明日が今日より輝いて
Let tomorrow shine brighter than today
幸せになれますように
And I hope to become happy
ちょっとくらい強がりな
Please forgive even...
ところも許してください
The parts of me that act a bit tough
逃げてちゃダメ
Don't run away
避けてちゃダメ
Don't avoid it
後悔なんてしたくない
I don't want to regret anything
レッツゴ　ハッピー
Let's go happy
らしく進もう
Let's move on as ourselves
なんで！？　ついてなくて
Why!? Not being lucky
へこんじゃう　レイニーデイ
A rainy day that makes me depressed
お気に入りの靴
My favorite shoes
水たまりガッカリ
Disappointed by a puddle
なのに突然　君が突然
But suddenly, you suddenly...
振り返ったその笑顔で
Turned around with that smile
熱くなっていく頬に
On my cheeks that are getting hot
気づかないでね
Please don't notice
君の手と手が触れ合って
Your hand and mine touching
伝わってるよ　オーマイスイート
It's being conveyed, oh my sweet
溢れ出すこの愛を
I want to nurture this overflowing love
甘い果実に育てたい！
Into a sweet fruit!
今日うまく行かなくたって
Even if things don't go well today
明日から変われるように
So that I can change from tomorrow
ちょっとだけ弱気でも
Even if I'm just a little timid
私を照らしてください
Please shine a light on me
涙ふいて　上を向いて
Wipe your tears, look up
止まってなんていられない
I can't just stay still
レッツゴ　ハッピー
Let's go happy
らしく進もう
Let's move on as ourselves
昨日までの自分にさよならなな
Saying goodbye to who I was until yesterday
明日はきっと明日のもっと
Tomorrow for sure, even more of tomorrow
太陽が照らすよ
The sun will shine on
君が好き！素直になって
I like you! If I could be honest
言えたらどんなに SO HAPPY
and say it, I'd be so happy
溢れ出すこの愛は
This overflowing love
甘いだけではありません！
is not just sweet!
明日が今日より輝いて
May tomorrow shine brighter than today
幸せになれますように
and may we become happy
ちょっとくらい強がりな
Even the parts of me
ところも許してください
that are a bit headstrong, please forgive them
逃げてちゃダメ避けてちゃダメ
Can't run away, can't avoid it
後悔なんてしたくない
I don't want any regrets
らしく進もう
I'll move forward in my own way
はい！ということで、皆さん！
Alright! So, everyone!
改めまして、にゃっはろー！
Once again, Nyahallo!
エリート巫女アイドルのさくらみこでーす！
It's elite shrine maiden idol Sakura Miko!
いや、ということで、ついに迎えた誕生日！
Wow, so my birthday is finally here!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、誕生日ということで皆さんこちらドドン！
Yes, since it's my birthday, everyone look at this, boom!
ハッシュタグさくらみこ生誕祭でたくさんツイートしてね！
Tweet a lot using the hashtag #さくらみこ生誕祭!
よろしくね！スクショもたくさんしてね！
Please do! Take lots of screenshots too!
はい！いや、みこ誕生日だからかな。
Yes! Wow, maybe it's because it's my birthday.
なんかステージが今までよりもパワーアップしていますよ！
The stage has powered up even more than before!
ドドン！
Boom!
うわあ！いや、さくら風が吹く青空です！
Whoa! Look, it's a blue sky with cherry blossom winds!
すごいね！いや、まだまだ仕掛けがありますけれども。
Amazing! Well, there are still more surprises.
いや、なんか鳥居もねドーンってなって、ゲートもドーンってなっております！
Look, the torii gate is like "bam!", and the gate is also "bam!"
たくさんありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
そして見て！
And look!
こちらさくら風で入場してきました、こちらの気球！
This balloon I rode in on with the cherry blossom wind!
みこぴーの気球だよ！
It's a Mikopi balloon!
いや、ついにみこぴーも今日まで育ちましたか。
Wow, Mikopi has finally grown up to this point.
いや、すごいね。嬉しいね。
Wow, that's amazing. I'm so happy.
いや、ありがとうございます。たくさんね。
Wow, thank you so much. Truly.
ということで、今回のライブはなんと！
So, for this live, believe it or not...
すごくたくさんゲストを呼んでおります！
I've invited a whole lot of guests!
そして、なんと後半には新衣装もお披露目しちゃうので！
And what's more, I'll be revealing a new outfit in the second half!
皆さん最後まで見逃すなよ！
So everyone, don't miss it until the very end!
それでは、ゲストパートいきますか！
Alright then, let's start the guest segment!
盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's get hyped!
腑抜けた心に I Need You
I need you for my spiritless heart
徒のアルカロイド
A useless alkaloid
あだ花 念写のシャッターチャンス かき鳴らすディストーション
A non-bearing flower, a thoughtography photo op, strumming distortion
付け焼き刃のサムライが 乱れ打つ三段銃
A makeshift samurai firing a matchlock volley
悲劇の歴史で踊ろうか
Shall we dance through tragic history?
ほら、テンペコヘンペコまいまい はあ！
Look, tempeko-hempeko-maimai. Ha!
僕の心はエゴロック 斜め45度ナンセンス
My heart is Ego Rock, a 45-degree slant of nonsense
ノウハウ砕いてマンネリを 明日にバイバイバイ
Crushing know-how and saying bye-bye-bye to the mundane tomorrow
バイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye
さあ、どこまでも生きようか
Well, shall we live as far as we can?
真夏並みHotなミュージック
Music as hot as midsummer
ハウツー砕いて丸書いて
Smash the how-to and draw a circle
明日もワッハッハ
Wah ha ha tomorrow too
洒落臭ぇのも癖になる
Even the cheeky stuff becomes a habit
はみ出しものだろう？
We're misfits, aren't we?
シニカルな視線の雨
A rain of cynical stares
今日も両目を開くふり
Pretending to open both eyes again today
不透明な感情は染まるだけさ
Opaque emotions just get stained
だったらいっそ見て見ぬふりする奴らを押し出せ
Then just push out those who turn a blind eye
人生かけたままごとです
It's playing house with our lives on the line
勝ち負けたりとも関せんぜ
I don't care about winning or losing
一歩砕いて常識は未来に Say Goodbye
Smash common sense and say goodbye to the future
僕の心はエゴロック
My heart is Egorock
斜め45度ナンセンス
A 45-degree angle of nonsense
ノウハウ砕いてマンネリを
Smash the know-how and the rut
明日にバイバイバイ
Bye bye bye to tomorrow
滑稽な生存者共
Ridiculous survivors
吐き気の空模様
Nauseating weather
シニカルな視線の雨
A rain of cynical stares
今日も両目を塞ぐふり
Pretending to cover both eyes again today
あ、あ、あ、マイクOK！
Ah, ah, ah, mic OK!
いくよー！
Here we go!
ミニスカで衝撃な
Shocking in a miniskirt
矢も射して衝撃だ
Even shot with an arrow, it's shocking
タイの晩餐 タイの晩餐
Thai dinner, Thai dinner
出待って待ってほら
Waiting at the stage door, look, wait
だだだだ 誰か告って頂戴よ
S-s-s-s-someone, please confess to me
ハイ！
High!
脱力系でクールに
Cool and relaxed
銃備え聞かせろ
Let them hear the gun ready
バリバリ中！
Full-throttle!
ビババビ
Viva Happy
切なくてもやるせなくても
Even if it's painful or miserable
カモンカモンカモンカモンカモンカモンボーイ！
Come on x6 boy!
あの子になんてなれないから
Because I can't become that girl
カモンカモンカモンカモンカモンカモンボーイ！
Come on x6 boy!
ありのままの自分を
If I can love myself
愛せればケセラセラ
as I am, Que Sera Sera
今はひとりぼっちな君に 君に
To you who are all alone now, to you
歌を 歌を あげる
I'll give you a song, a song
はいどうぞ！
Here you go!
ビビビビビビ ビババビバハピ
Bi-bi-bi-bi-bi-bi Viva-Happy
いやいや争い
No fighting, no
不干渉主義なの なのなのな
I'm for non-interference, non-non-interference
ビババビ
Viva Happy
コトコト煮出して
Simmering it down
ヘトヘトにした身を
to a worn-out body
ビビビビビビ ビババビバハピ
Bi-bi-bi-bi-bi-bi Viva-Happy
縛られてもせかされても
Whether tied down or rushed
カモンカモンカモンカモンカモンカモンボーイ！
Come on x6 boy!
ダッシュで結果求めすぎよ
Seeking results too fast with a dash
カモンカモンカモンカモンカモンカモンボーイ！
Come on x6 boy!
常識はいつまでも
Common sense is always
大人の不快なスラング
an adult's unpleasant slang
意識の宇宙から 君に 君に
From the universe of consciousness, to you, to you
届く 届く サイン
a sign will reach you, reach you
ジャジャジャジャン
Ta-da!
ビビビビビビ ビババビバハピ
Bi-bi-bi-bi-bi-bi Viva-Happy
ぐだぐだ遂に
Rambling on, finally
自意識はわっはっは
self-consciousness is wah ha ha
事情はほら じじばば
The circumstances, you see, old men and women
ビババビバハピ
Viva Happy
あれこれしたいけど
I want to do this and that, but
曖昧見舞いキリマイ
Vague visits, Kirimai
ハッピーに振る舞う
Behaving happily
君が好きだよ
I love you
中二病のビバ
Eighth-grader syndrome Viva
ちょっとライブ鬼畜
A bit of a brutal live
中途半端なお説教きた
Half-baked preaching arrived
そんなに世間は甘くないだから
The world isn't that sweet
どんなに世間は甘くない夢見て
Dreaming of how the world isn't sweet
ブルダバダーン
Burudabadaan
バケツ・ピーナッツ・ブースト・ペースで GO！
Bucket, peanuts, boost, pace, GO!
にゃん
Nyan (Meow)
ビビビビビビ ビババビバハピ
Bi-bi-bi-bi-bi-bi Viva-Happy
ビバビバハッピー
Viva viva happy
ポロポロ涙して
Tears falling down
そんなに世間は甘くない
The world isn't that soft
ビバ！
Viva!
ワンツースリーに落ちていくシャンデリア
A chandelier falling down on one, two, three
一斉に火をともすネオンライト
Neon lights lighting up all at once
ファンファーレ鳴き出すテセラクラウン
Fanfare howling, Tessera Crown
スポットライト浴びて
Bathed in the spotlight
さあ早くここで踊れ
Now, hurry and dance here
開演さ、イッツ・ショータイム
The show begins, it's showtime
ショウタイム・ルーラー
Showtime Ruler
黙々とステップ踏んで
Silently stepping
有毒な視線は向こうの方
Toxic stares are over there
深呼吸ちょっと
A quick breath
心臓はビートを刻むほら
Listen, the heart is beating
キュー・アクション
Cue, action
正解へ上がっていく
Rising up to the correct answer
内面を煽っていく
Stirring up the inner self
知能を解き放つ頃
When it's time to release intelligence
一瞬へ、レッツ・ショータイム
Into an instant, let's showtime
ショウタイム・ルーラー
Showtime Ruler
Ah Ah 僕の感性
Ah Ah My sensitivity
Ah Ah 妄想中
Ah Ah In a delusion
Ah Ah 君の感性
Ah Ah Your sensitivity
Ah Ah 挑戦中
Ah Ah Challenging
Ah Ah 研ぎ澄ましていく
Ah Ah Sharpening it
Ah Ah この一瞬
Ah Ah This moment
君の感情を支配するショウタイム
Showtime that dominates your emotions
ルーラルーラルーラ
Ruler Ruler Ruler
イッツ・ショータイム・ハイヤー・ハイヤー・ハイヤー
It's Showtime Higher higher higher
イッツ・ショータイム・クレイジー・クレイジー・クレイジーにしちゃって
It's Showtime, make it crazy crazy crazy
ショウタイム・ルーラルーラルーラ
Showtime Ruler Ruler Ruler
イッツ・ショータイム・ハイヤー・ハイヤー・ハイヤー
It's Showtime Higher higher higher
イッツ・ショータイム・夢中に・夢中に・ショータイム
It's Showtime, obsessed, obsessed
夢みたいな時間
A dreamlike time
さあもっと声を聴かせて頂戴な
Now, please let me hear your voice more
ワンツーではやる感情の合図だ
A signal of emotions that hurries at one-two
君を飲み込んでさ
Swallowing you up
正負も悲哀も歓喜も五感の思い通り
Positives and negatives, sorrow and joy, all as the five senses wish
二度と孤独になんてなれないよ
I can never be lonely again
僕の合図で
At my signal
君は合図オンステージ
You are the signal on stage
ショウタイム・ショウタイム・さあ一つになって
Showtime, showtime, now become one
響け君のアンセム
Let your anthem resound
感情から揺さぶるアンセム
An anthem that shakes from emotions
泣きそうなほどに重なって
Overlapping so much it makes me want to cry
喜怒哀楽アンダー・ザ・コントロール
Emotions under control
今僕らの想いは連動
Now our feelings are linked
君の鼓動 最速にする ショウタイム
Showtime that makes your heartbeat the fastest
僕らを繋ぐよショウタイム
Showtime that connects us
ルーラルーラルーラ
Ruler Ruler Ruler
イッツ・ショータイム・ハイヤー・ハイヤー・ハイヤー
It's Showtime Higher higher higher
イッツ・ショータイム・クレイジー・クレイジー・クレイジーにしちゃって
It's Showtime, make it crazy crazy crazy
ショウタイム・ルーラルーラルーラ
Showtime Ruler Ruler Ruler
イッツ・ショータイム・ハイヤー・ハイヤー・ハイヤー
It's Showtime Higher higher higher
イッツ・ショータイム・夢中に・夢中に・ショータイム
It's Showtime, obsessed, obsessed
夢みたいな時間
A dreamlike time
可愛くてごめん
Sorry for being so cute
私は私のことを愛して何が悪いの？嫉妬でしょうか？
What's wrong with me loving myself? Is it jealousy?
痛いだとか変わってるとか届きませんね。そのリプライ
Those replies saying I'm painful or strange won't reach me
大好きなお洋服
My favorite clothes
大好きなお化粧で
With my favorite makeup
お決まりのハーフツインまいて
Curling my usual half-twins
お出かけしよう
Let's go out
日傘持ってぼっちだって幸せだもん
I'm happy even alone with a parasol
可愛くてごめん
I'm Sorry for Being So Cute
チュ！
Chu!
可愛くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so cute
生まれてきちゃってごめん
I'm sorry for being born
チュ！
Chu!
あざとくてごめん
I'm sorry for being so calculated
気になっちゃうよね？ごめん
You're curious about me, right? Sorry
チュ！
Chu!
可愛くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so cute
努力しちゃってごめん
I'm sorry for working so hard
チュ！
Chu!
尊くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so precious
女子力高くてごめん
I'm sorry for my high femininity
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁｗ
It makes you mad, doesn't it? Serves you right!
貴方は貴方の事だけど
You are yourself, but
どうぞ私に干渉しないでください
Please don't interfere with me
類は友を呼ぶと言うけど
They say birds of a feather flock together
届きませんねその陰口
But I can't hear your backbiting
重い厚底ブーツ
Heavy platform boots
お気に入りの服ね
My favorite clothes
崩せない前髪
Bangs that can't be messed up
櫛で解いて
Combed into place
お出かけしよ
Let's go out
軽い女？ふざけんな
An easy woman? Don't mess with me
重すぎるっつの
I'm saying it's way too heavy
チュ！
Chu!
可愛くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so cute
この時代生きてごめん
I'm sorry for living in this era
チュ！
Chu!
目立っちゃってごめん
I'm sorry for standing out
意識しちゃうよね？ごめん
You're conscious of me, right? Sorry
チュ！
Chu!
可愛くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so cute
自分磨きしてごめん
I'm sorry for working on myself
チュ！
Chu!
ぶりっ子でごめん
I'm sorry for acting innocent
虜にしちゃってごめん
I'm sorry for making you fall for me
ムカついちゃうでしょ？ざまぁｗ
It makes you mad, doesn't it? Serves you right!
趣味も次第　変わり者と
Depending on my hobbies, I'm just called
ばかりされても
an eccentric all the time, but
曲げたくない　怖くもない
I don't want to change, and I'm not afraid
あんたら如き
of people like you
自分の味方は自分でありたい
I want to be my own ally
一番大切にしてあげたい
I want to cherish myself the most
理不尽な我慢はさせたくない
I don't want to force unreasonable endurance
それが私
That's me
チュ！
Chu!
可愛くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so cute
生まれてきちゃってごめん
I'm sorry for being born
チュ！
Chu!
あざとくてごめん
I'm sorry for being so calculated
人生楽しんでごめん
I'm sorry for enjoying my life
チュ！
Chu!
可愛くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so cute
努力しちゃってごめん
I'm sorry for working so hard
チュ！
Chu!
尊くてごめん
I'm sorry for being so precious
女子力高くてごめん
I'm sorry for my high femininity
ムカついちゃうよね？ざまぁｗ
It makes you mad, doesn't it? Serves you right!
わたしの一番かわいいところ
My Most Adorable Aspect
あれ？気付いちゃいましたか？
Oh? Did you notice?
生まれて30秒で最初に聞いた言葉は
The first words I heard 30 seconds after birth were
「おたまじゃくし」？それ覚えてないけど嬉しかったはず
'Tadpole'? I don't remember that, but I must've been happy
今でもだいたいのことは変わってないっていうか、そりゃ
Even now, most things haven't changed, I mean
髪は染めていますのでその辺も評価！
I've dyed my hair, so evaluate that too!
お願い！携帯のアンテナを光らせて
Please! Make the cell phone antenna glow
それが超キュートなあの頃だって知ってたり
Knowing that was that super cute era
令和か？アンテナって何って言ってるのな！
Is this Reiwa? You're asking what an antenna is?!
私に付き合ってくれるの好き？
Do you like spending time with me?
逆にでも私のどこが好き？
On the other hand, what do you like about me?
ねえねえねえ！わたしの一番かわいいところに気付いてる？
Hey, hey, hey! Have you noticed my most adorable aspect?
そんな君が一番すごよ！すごく好きよ！すごくスキル！
You're the most amazing for that! I like you so much! Such skills!
そして君が知ってる私が一番かわいいの！
And the 'me' that you know is the most adorable!
私はそれに気付いた！
I've realized that!
だからそれかわいい　あれかわいいなんて
So saying that's cute or this is cute
誰かわいい　それかわいいなんて
Or who's cute or what's cute
言わないで　私以外なんてやだ！
Don't say it! I can't stand anyone but me being it!
なんで？ねえねえねえ！
Why? Hey, hey, hey!
私気づいちゃいました！
I've noticed something!
毎日何十分も
Dozens of minutes every day
眺められなくなってお菓子は
I can't stop looking at them, and sweets
他よりちょっと甘くなるって
become a bit sweeter than others...
前に言っていたような
is what you said before.
さすがにそれは嘘だろな
Surely that's a lie,
けど私は言われたいタイプでして
but I'm the type who wants to be told that.
もっと分かりやすくていいんだよ
It's okay to be more straightforward.
お待ちしてましょう
I'll be waiting.
お願い！
Please!
何しててもどんな顔見せてても
No matter what I'm doing or what face I'm making,
いつもチャンキュートだって
you've always been sure
確信してるのは
that I'm cute.
なんかさ知らなかったタイプの運命の
Is it some kind of destiny
ひとつなの？
I didn't know about?
好き勝手は無理、ごめん
Doing as you please is impossible, sorry.
逆にでもそれより楽しいよ
But conversely, it's more fun than that.
ねえねえねえ！
Hey, hey, hey!
私の一番かわいいところをよく見てる
You're looking closely at my best part.
そんな君が本当にチョーラッキーな人すぎる
You're truly such a lucky person.
そして君が何年経ってもそう思えるように
And so that you can feel that way for years to come,
私はそれに気づいた
I realized that.
あの時もどうだいな表情してる
You're making an expression like that time too.
届かぬ気持ち悪いくらい想像しちゃうかな
Maybe I'll imagine so much it's almost gross.
それ可愛い、あれ可愛いよって
Saying that's cute, that one's cute...
本当に可愛いって言って
Tell me it's really cute.
言って！
Say it!
私の一番かわいいところに気づいてる
You've noticed my best part.
そんな君が一番すごいすごいよ凄すぎる
You're the best, best, just too incredible.
そして君が知ってる私が一番かわいいの
And the "me" that you know is the cutest.
私もそれに気づいた
I realized that too.
私の一番かわいいところをよく見てる
You're looking closely at my best part.
そんな君が本当にチョーラッキーな人すぎる
You're truly such a lucky person.
そして君が何年経ってもそう思えるように
And so that you can feel that way for years to come,
私はそれに気づいた
I realized that.
だから私の一番かわいいところに気づいてる
So, you've noticed my best part.
そんな君が一番すごいすごいよ凄すぎる
You're the best, best, just too incredible.
そして君が知ってる私が一番かわいいの
And the "me" that you know is the cutest.
私もそれに気づいた
I realized that too.
だからそれ可愛い、あれ可愛いなんて
So saying "that's cute, this is cute"
あれ可愛い、それ可愛いなんて
saying "this is cute, that's cute"
言わないで私以外なんて
don't say it to anyone but me.
やだ！
No!
なんてあげない
I won't give you to anyone.
いくぞー！
Here we go!
アユミ☆マジカルショータイム
Ayumi☆Magical Showtime
モノクロだらけの明日なんて
A tomorrow full of monochrome,
空白だらけの世界なんて
a world full of blank spaces,
笑顔さえも枯れちゃいそうで
even smiles seem to wither away.
なんてたって大嫌い！
I hate it so much!
虹色だらけの地図を描こう
Let's draw a map full of rainbow colors.
キラキラだらけに塗りつぶそう
Let's paint it all over with sparkles.
夢の魔法使い目指して
Aiming to be a dream magician,
今日も修行中！
I'm training today too!
魔法の呪文を唱えまshow
Let's chant a magic spell.
カラフル・マジックをご覧あれ
Take a look at colorful magic.
よし、は、てい、あーれ、うそー、よいしょ、えー、はえ、うわー！
Alright, ha, tei, ah-re, no way, yoisho, eh, hae, uwaah!
いくよー！
Here I go!
マジカル・ポルパ・ペルカ
Magical Polpa Pelka
見てみてみんな
Look, everyone,
It's ショータイム！
It's showtime!
ワンツー・スリーで染め上げて
Dye it all in one, two, three.
ビビッド・カラフル・パーフェクトだから
Because it's vivid, colorful, and perfect!
マジカル・ポルパ・ペルカ
Magical Polpa Pelka
夢色世界にご招待！
Welcome to a dream-colored world!
笑顔咲かせるような
Like a blooming smile,
君だけの魔法をかけよう
I'll cast a spell just for you.
内緒だよ、ちゅっ
It's a secret, chu!
2曲までもう少し待ってね♪
Wait a bit more for the second song♪
時には遅めのステップで
Sometimes with slower steps,
優しいメロディに揺られ
swaying to a gentle melody.
輝く音色を奏でるのも
Playing a shining tone...
なんてたって大好き
I love it after all.
やっぱり早めで遅れないで
As expected, go faster and don't be late.
ワクワク鼓動は待ってくれない
The exciting heartbeat won't wait.
夢の魔法使い目指して
Aiming to be a dream magician,
今日も修行中！
I'm training today too!
魔法のリズムを奏でまshow
Let's play a magical rhythm.
もうひとつマジックをご覧あれ
Take a look at one more magic trick.
よし、は、てい、あーれ、うそー、よいしょ、えー！
Alright, ha, tei, ah-re, no way, yoisho, eh!
いっくぞー！
Let's go!
こーだー！
Come on!
マジカ・ポパペルカ
Magica Popaperka
ほらほら みんな It's Showtime!
Look, look, everyone, it's Showtime!
1, 2, 3 で塗りまくれ
Paint it all at 1, 2, 3
ビビット・カラフル・カルテットから
From the vivid colorful quartet
マジカ・ポパペルカ
Magica Popaperka
夢色世界にご招待！
An invitation to a dream-colored world!
涙 吹き飛ばそうよ
Let's blow away the tears
弾けだす 魔法を唱えよう
Let's chant the magic that starts to burst
待ってたんだよ
I've been waiting for you
間奏
Interlude
休憩タイム みこの好きなところコメントしてー！
Break time! Comment your favorite things about Miko!
あれあれ また私の 魅力が伝わってない？
Oh dear, has my charm still not gotten across?
これだけじゃ終われない！ 最後に、とびきりショータイム！
It's not over yet! Finally, the best showtime!
まだ信じてない人は お気をつけください
If you still don't believe, please be careful
超最強の 禁断呪文
The strongest forbidden spell
超生物生成魔法 (ハイパービッグバン・ポパペルカ)
Super-lifeform Creation Magic (Hyper Big Bang Popaperka)
てててー やったぜ！
Ta-da! I did it!
マジカ・ポパペルカ
Magica Popaperka
見て見て みんな It's Showtime!
Look, look, everyone, it's Showtime!
1, 2, 3 で染めあげて
Dye it all at 1, 2, 3
ビビット・カラフル・カルテットから
From the vivid colorful quartet
マジカ・ポパペルカ
Magica Popaperka
夢色世界にご招待！
An invitation to a dream-colored world!
笑顔 咲かせるような
Let's cast a magic just for you
君だけの 魔法をかけよう
That makes smiles bloom
内緒だよ
It's a secret
ふふっ
Hehe
少女レイ
作詞・作曲 みきとP
Shoujo Rei
Lyrics & Music: MikitoP
本能が狂い始める
Instincts begin to go mad
追い詰められた二十日鼠
A cornered house mouse
そう、君は友達
Yes, you are my friend
僕の手を掴めよ
Take my hand
そう、君は独りさ
Yes, you are all alone
居場所なんてないだろう
There is no place for you, is there?
二人きり、このまま
The two of us, just like this
愛し合えるさ
Can love each other
繰り返すフラッシュバック
Repeating flashbacks
蝉の声
Cicadas' cries
二度と帰らぬ君
You'll never return
空回り、千切れてく
Spinning in circles, tearing apart
お揃いのキーホルダー
The matching keychains
夏が消し去った
Summer erased
白い肌の少女に
To the girl with white skin
哀しいほど
To a sad extent
憑りつかれてしまいたい
I want to be possessed by her
本能が暴れ始める
Instincts begin to run wild
九月のスタート告げるチャイム
The chime that signals the start of September
そう、君が悪いんだよ
Yes, it's your fault
僕だけを見ててよ
Only look at me
そう、君の苦しみに
Yes, for your suffering
助けが欲しいだろう
You want help, don't you?
溺れてく その手に
To the hand that's drowning
そっとキスをした
I gently kissed
薄紅のけものたち
Pale crimson beasts
その心晴れるまで
Until that heart clears up
爪を突き立ててる
Digging in claws
追憶のスカート
The skirt of reminiscence
夏の静寂を
Summer's silence
切り裂くような悲鳴が
A scream that seems to tear through
木霊する 教室の窓には
Echoing in the classroom window
青空
Is the blue sky
君は友達
You are my friend
さあ 僕は友達 僕の手を掴めよ
Now, I am your friend, take my hand.
さあ 君がいなくちゃ 居場所なんてないんだよ
Now, without you, there's no place for me.
透き通った世界で 愛し合えたらな
If only we could love each other in this transparent world.
繰り返すフラッシュバック 蝉の声 二度と帰らぬ君
Recurring flashbacks, the sound of cicadas, you who will never return.
永遠に千切れていく お揃いのキーホルダー
Our matching keychains, torn apart forever.
夏が消し去った 白い肌の少女に
To the girl with white skin that summer erased,
哀しいほど 取り憑かれてしまいたい
I want to be possessed to a sorrowful degree.
透明な君は 僕を指差してた
You, transparent, were pointing at me.
はーい！ということで、ここまでライブやってきましたが
Hi! And so, we've had the live performance up to this point...
みんな、見て！ジャジャーン！
Everyone, look! Ta-da!
新衣装お披露目しました！
I've revealed my new outfit!
可愛いでしょー！
Isn't it cute?
いや、あ、こちらね、ピンクのセーラー服となっております。
Well, yes, it's a pink sailor uniform.
みこの一番のお気に入りはね、このベレー帽！
Miko's favorite part is this beret!
可愛いでしょー、可愛いでしょー。えへへ、えへへ。
It's cute, right? It's cute, right? Ehehe, ehehe.
はい！ということで、なんと、実はまだお披露目があるんですよ！
Yes! And so, believe it or not, there's actually more to reveal!
えー、気になる？
Oh, curious?
それがこちら！はい！
It's this! Yes!
ということで、みこの新オリジナルソングが出ます！
And so, Miko's new original song is coming out!
この曲はね、みこの大好きな『冴えない彼女の育てかた』の
This song was written by Sawai Miku-san, who worked on the
オープニングなどを手掛けている沢井美空さんに作っていただきました！
opening of my favorite "Saekano"!
ありがとうございます！いやー、とっても嬉しい！
Thank you very much! Wow, I'm so happy!
もう本当に大好きなのでね、本当に本当にいい曲なので、ぜひ聴いてください！
I really love it, and it's a truly great song, so please listen to it!
本日の3月5日の24時から、楽曲配信されるので、皆さんチェックしてね！
It will be released today, March 5th, at midnight, so everyone check it out!
ということで、このあと、なんとその曲を歌っちゃいます！
And so, after this, I'm actually going to sing that song!
それでは皆さん、聴いてください。『ハートオンライン』！
Now then, everyone, please listen. "Heart Online"!
1, 2!
ハートオンライン
作詞・作曲・編曲：沢井美空
Heart Online
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Miku Sawai
言いかけた言葉も飲み込んで
Swallowing the words I was about to say,
あれっ不具合(バグ)かな ストップしちゃって
oh, is it a bug? I just stopped.
何も言わなくたって君は なんでも分かってくれるけど
Even if I don't say anything, you understand everything, but...
カッコつけてもつかなくて 失敗ばかりでごめんね
Even when I try to look cool, I can't. I'm sorry for all the mistakes.
だけど言いたいことがあるの
But there's something I want to say.
もうちょっと あとちょっと 強くなりたいな
A little bit more, just a little bit more, I want to become stronger...
君のためならね
...if it's for you.
1, 2 ハートオンライン 気持ちまるごと
1, 2, Heart Online, all my feelings...
乗せる電波 伝わるかな？
...will the radio waves carry them to you?
大好きだって 大切だって
I love you, you're important.
ホントはいつも言いたいのに
I always want to say it, but...
きっとね きっと 会えなくても
Surely, surely, even if we can't meet,
君とだから 繋がれるよ
because it's you, we can connect.
ひらひらと舞う 君がくれた
Fluttering and dancing, the hearts you gave me...
ハートが集まって
...gather,
サクラになる
and become cherry blossoms.
分岐ルートで戸惑うたび
Whenever I'm lost at a fork in the road
正解なんてわかんないけど
I don't know what the right answer is
一緒に探し当てた今日に
But to this day we found together
いつも胸がいっぱいになるの
My heart is always full
ひとりだけ立ち止まっても
Even if I'm the only one standing still
そんな気がしても夜に
Even if it feels like that in the night
キミが見せてくれた景色に
By the scenery you showed me
もう一歩 あと一歩 踏み出してみたいな
I want to take one more step, another step forward
そう思えたんだ
That's what I thought
ぜんぶオンライン ダメなところも
Everything online, even the bad parts
キミなら笑ってくれるよね？
You'll laugh it off, won't you?
着飾りよりもありのままで
Being myself rather than dressing up
そんな勇気もくれたから
Because you gave me that courage
きっとね きっと 挫けそうでも
Surely, surely, even if I'm about to give up
何度だって花開くよ
I'll bloom again and again
ひらひらと舞う キミがくれた
Fluttering and dancing, the heart you gave me...
ハートが集まって
Collects together and...
さくらになる
Becomes a cherry blossom
舞い落ちて雨に流れる
Falling and flowing in the rain
そんな一時のユメでも
Even if it's just a fleeting dream
まつ毛の先 ふわり触れて
Softly touching the tips of my eyelashes
煌めいた キミがいた さくら色のイマが
The cherry-blossom colored 'now' where you were sparkled
宝物だから
Because it's a treasure
ハートオンライン 気持ちまるごと
Heart Online, my feelings as a whole
乗せる電波 伝わるかな？
Will the radio waves carry them to you?
大好きだって 大切だって
That I love you, that you're precious
ホントの気持ち伝えるよ
I'll tell you my true feelings
きっとね きっと 会えなくても
Surely, surely, even if we can't meet
キミとだから繋がれるよ
I can connect with you because it's you
ひらひらと舞う キミがくれた
Fluttering and dancing, the heart you gave me...
ハートが集まって
Collects together and...
さくらになる
Becomes a cherry blossom
これが、最後の曲です！
This is the last song!
今日は誕生日祝ってくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for celebrating my birthday today!
見てください、誇り高きアイドル。
Please listen, Hokori Takaki Idol.
私のこと知ってますか？
Do you know me?
可愛く見えてますか？
Do I look cute?
私の歌どうだろうな
How is my singing?
うまく歌えてますか？
Am I singing well?
衣装だとかメイクだとか
My outfit, my makeup...
可愛く見えてますか？
Do I look cute?
振付とかファンサとかも
The choreography, the fan service...
喜んでもらえますか？
Are you happy with them?
手は冷たくなって
My hands go cold
足は震える
My legs shake
それでも歌いたい
But I still want to sing
アイドルだから
Because I'm an idol
バカにする奴は嫌いだ
I hate people who make fun of others
独断されるのも嫌いだ
I hate being judged arbitrarily
アイドルなんかという言葉を 見てもいないくせに言うな
Don't say "just an idol" when you haven't even seen us
頑張りを当然と言うな
Don't say our hard work is a given
イメージとか強制するな
Don't force images on us
“アイドルなんか”という言葉は この世で一番大嫌いだ
The phrase "just an idol" is what I hate most in this world
プライベート見えないから
You can't see my private life
分からないと思います
So you probably don't know
性格とか悪い方です
My personality is actually kind of bad
騙しちゃっていますか？
Am I deceiving you?
でも本気です 本気なんです
But I'm serious, I'm for real
ありのままの私を
Please like me as I am
好きになって推してください
Please support me
それってワガママですか？
Is that selfish of me?
きっと可愛くない
I'm sure I'm not cute
全部分かってる
I know all about it
それでも好かれてたい
But I still want to be liked
アイドルだから
Because I'm an idol
皮肉言う奴は嫌いだ
I hate people who are cynical
言い訳ばかりも嫌いだ
I hate making excuses all the time too
こんなもんかという言葉を軽々しく口にするな
Don't say things like "Is this all?" so lightly
勝手に限界決めるな
Don't decide the limits on your own
笑い者になんてするな
Don't make me a laughingstock
アイドルなんかという言葉はこの世で一番大嫌いだ
The phrase "just an idol" is what I hate most in this world
向かい風も切り裂け 誇り高きアイドル
Cutting through even the headwind, a proud idol
目指そうぜ
Let's aim for it
お金がなければ活動できない
I can't be active if I don't have money
好きな事ばかりじゃ生きてはいけない
I can't live on just the things I like
元気あげるはずがもらってばかりだし
I'm supposed to give energy, but I'm just receiving it instead
恩返しできる日まで待ってて
Wait for me until the day I can repay you
待ってて
Wait for me
歓声が減っても 飽きられちゃっても
Even if the cheers fade, even if people get tired of me
それでも笑っていたい
I still want to keep smiling
アイドルだから
Because I'm an idol
熱いファンの愛があって
With the passion of the fans
スタッフさんの愛があって
With the love of the staff
いつも家族の愛があって
Always with the love of my family
生きてるアイドル
An idol who lives
バカにする奴は嫌いだ
I hate those who make fun of me
見下されるのも嫌いだ
I hate being looked down upon too
アイドルなんかという言葉を見てもいないくせに言うな
Don't use the phrase "just an idol" when you haven't even seen what I do
頑張りを当然と言うな
Don't call hard work "natural"
イメージとか強制するな
Don't force an image on me
アイドルなんかという言葉はこの世で一番大嫌いだ
The phrase "just an idol" is what I hate most in this world
みんな、いつもありがとう！
Everyone, thank you as always!
これからも頑張るから、応援よろしくね！
I'll keep doing my best, so please support me!
大好きなんだよ！
I love you!
はーい！
Haaai!
ということでみなさーん、ライブ楽しんでもらえましたかー？
So everyone, did you enjoy the live?
たくさんお祝いしてくれて、本当にありがとー！
Thank you so much for celebrating with me!
えー、先ほど披露した「ハートオンライン」はこのあと24時から配信開始なので、ぜひダウンロードしてね！
Um, "Heart Online," which I just performed, will be available for streaming starting at midnight, so please download it!
そして、最後にドドドンと告知でーす！
And finally, a big announcement!
この度なんと、さくらみこ、明利酒類さんとのコラボが決定しましたー！
This time, Sakura Miko's collaboration with Meiri Shurui has been decided!
その名も、「酔うたい焼き さくらみこすぺしゃる」！
Its name is "You Taiyaki Sakura Miko Special"!
酔うたい焼き さくらみこすぺしゃる
You Taiyaki Sakura Miko Special
明利酒類さんで発売のたい焼きリキュール「酔うたい焼き」をみこイメージでさくら風味にしていただいた限定商品です！
It's a limited edition product where Meiri Shurui's "You Taiyaki" liqueur was given a cherry blossom flavor with an image of Miko!
わー！ありがとうございます！
Wow! Thank you very much!
えー、ラベルのイラストはさとうぽてさんに描き下ろしていただきましたー！
Um, the label illustration was newly drawn by Sato Pote-san!
お値段、税込なんと、3500円！
The price is, including tax, 3,500 yen!
三日後の3月8日水曜日、17時から明利酒類さんのオンラインショップにて発売予定なので、お楽しみにー！
It's scheduled to be released on Meiri Shurui's online shop from 5 PM on Wednesday, March 8th, three days from now, so look forward to it!
さらにさらに！こちら！ドン！
More and more! This! Boom!
誕生日記念 2023 3月5日 販売開始
Birthday Memorial 2023 March 5th Sale Start
みこの誕生日記念グッズが出まーす！
Miko's birthday memorial goods are coming out!
わー！続々詳細を見ていくぞー！
Wow! Let's check out the details one by one!
2層アクリルパネル
2-Layer Acrylic Panel
はい、ということでこちら！2層アクリルパネル！
Yes, so here it is! 2-layer acrylic panel!
えー、新衣装のみこを書いてもらいました！おるだん先生、いつもありがとう！
Um, I had them draw Miko in her new outfit! Ordan-sensei, thank you as always!
みこちとおそろいリュックサック
Matching Backpack with Mikochi
そして！みこちとおそろいリュックサック！
And! A matching backpack with Mikochi!
あの新衣装のね、みこのリュックが命がけです！
That new outfit's... Miko's backpack is for real!
まあね、ここにね、みこぴーのぬいぐるみをボーンと入れてもよし！
Well, you can also put a Mikopi plushie in here like "bam"!
35P着ぐるみマスコットキーホルダー
35P Kigurumi Mascot Key Holder
そして！35P着ぐるみマスコットキーホルダー！
And! 35P Kigurumi Mascot Key Holder!
みこが35Pの着ぐるみをしています！かわいい！
Miko is wearing a 35P kigurumi! Cute!
タンブラー
Tumbler
そして、こちらタンブラー！これはね、普段使いしてもらいたいなと思っております！
And here's a tumbler! I hope you'll use this for everyday use!
もうずっと作りたかった！イエーイ！使ってね！
I've wanted to make one for a long time! Yay! Please use it!
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Memorial Full Set
そして、フルセット！
And, the full set!
フルセット購入特典は、なんと！数量限定で、直筆サイン入り！
The full set purchase bonus is, wow! A limited quantity with a hand-written signature!
フルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
頑張って書くぞー！書くぞ、書くぞー！
I'll do my best to write them! I'll write, I'll write!
ということで、こちらおるだん先生描き下ろしイラストのポストカードが付いてきまーす！
So, this includes a postcard with an illustration newly drawn by Ordan-sensei!
あ、数量限定間に合わなくても、箔押しサインとかはですね、
Ah, even if you don't make it for the limited edition,
あの、用意してありますので、ぜひ、あの、安心してください。
I've prepared foil-stamped signatures and such, so please rest assured.
でも、すぐに買ってね！間に合うからね！頑張ってね！はい。
But buy it soon! You can still make it! Good luck! Yes.
そして、皆さん、怒涛の告知、いかがでしたでしょうかー！
And everyone, how did you like that flurry of announcements!
いやー、怒涛でしたねー。ねー。
Man, that was intense. Right?
でもね、この後はなんと、まだまだあります。メインで、
But wait, there's more after this. On the main channel,
なんとガチ恋、ガチ、ガチ恋限定シチュエーションの
we're having a Gachikoi, Gachi, Gachikoi-only situation
配信をするので、いや、照れますけどね。
stream, so... man, it's embarrassing though.
需要あるのかって感じですけどね。ぜひ皆さん、見に来てねー！
I wonder if there's even a demand for it. Everyone, please come watch!
それでは、みんな誕生日お祝いしてくれてありがとう！
Well then, thank you everyone for celebrating my birthday!
大好きだよ！バイバーイ！
I love you! Bye-bye!
みんなー！今日もありがとうおお！！
Everyone! Thank you so much for today!!
みこを見つけてくれて、好きになってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for finding Miko and falling in love with me!
これからも！笑顔いっぱい咲かせていこうねーっ！！🌸
Let's keep making many smiles bloom from now on too!! 🌸